Now, I'm going to show you how to make one of my favorite holiday punches.
This is called the non-alcoholic Spiced Punch and it's very quick and easy to make.
But, so good.
You're going to need four cups of cranberry juice, honey just for the taste, a few sticks of cinnamon, a pinch of nutmeg and about three to four cloves.
Now, I'm going to bring over here my punch bowl to mix all the things in.
And, you can start your stove top at about medium.
Now, I'm going to mix the two cinnamon sticks with the four cups of cranberry juice.
Like I said, just a little hint of nutmeg and a few cloves.
Like so.
And, we're going to get our wooden spoon.
Just mix all of the ingredients together.
So, you can get acquainted with one another.
And, we're going to take it over to our stove top where our sauce pan will be ready to go and on medium.
Let's go over there.
So, in the pan we're going to be heating our four cups of cranberry juice with the cloves, the hint of nutmeg and the cinnamon sticks.
And, we're going to add some honey.
We need to make sure that we stir until the honey as completely dissolved.
And, of course the juice is nice and warm.
That should be enough.
But, if you like honey, feel free to add a little more.
Now, we're going to bring the punch over to our bowl.
Make sure you do it very gently, so you don't get burned.
The non-alcoholic Spiced Punch serves six to eight people.
And, typically it would be served in a mug or a teacup garnished with about two little sticks of cinnamon and that's it.
The non-alcoholic Spiced Punch.